A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Secretary's Office, Biographical Files, RG 15 FA1280
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Staff, A-Z, 1940s-1960s; 1; 42.05 Cubic Feet 32 record storage boxes
  - Leidner, Irene (Box 18)
  - Leigh, Ralph E. (Box 18)
  - Leland, Beatrice (Box 18)
  - Lemont, Barbara (Box 18)
  - Lenert, Louva G. (Box 18)
  - Lenette, Edwin H. (Box 18)
  - Leonard, Ann (Box 18)
  - Leonard, Irving A. (Box 18)
  - Lethen, Barbara A. (Box 18)
  - Lewandowski, Thaddeus (Box 18)
  - Lewerth, Catherine (Box 18)
  - Lewis, Hilldegard (Box 18)
  - Lewis, Paul A. (Box 18)
  - Lewis, Jane R. (Box 18)
  - Lhamon, Mary B. (Box 18)
  - Li, Ming Yu (Box 18)
  - Liebeskind, Sandra (Box 18)
  - Liener, Irvin E. (Box 18)
  - Liker, George (Box 18)
  - Lincoln, Ruth M. (Box 18)
  - Linden, Jean C. (Box 18)
  - Lindhard, Elsa A. (Box 18)
  - Linton, Alice (Box 18)
  - Lissy, John C. (Box 18)
  - Lister, Beverly E. (Box 18)
  - Little, Elizabeth G. (Box 18)
  - Litts, Donald (Box 18)
  - Lloyd, Wray (Box 18)
  - Lloyd, Wray (Mrs.) (Box 18)
  - Lockway, Gertrude (Box 18)
  - Lockwood, Carolyn (Box 18)
  - Lodato, Irene (Box 18)
  - Loeb, Robert F. (Box 18)
  - Lofttus, Louise (Box 18)
  - Long, Alice (Box 18)
  - Long, John J. (Box 18)
  - Long, Rudolph (Box 18)
  - Longhurst, William M. (Box 18)
  - Longley, Frances F. (Box 18)
  - Loofbourow, John R. (Box 18)
  - Loomes, Leila (Box 18)
  - Loomis, William Farnsworth (Box 18)
  - Loring, Alfred J. (Box 19)
  - Lotz, Ruth (Box 19)
  - Lounsbury, Jane N. (Box 19)
  - Lovecky, Georgene (Box 19)
  - Lovell, Robin (Box 19)
  - Lovellette, Marjorie N. (Box 19)
  - Lowe, Catherine N. (Box 19)
  - Lowell, Paul M. (Box 19)
  - Lowell, Robert (Box 19)
  - Lowery, Marcella (Box 19)
  - Lun, G. Lee (Box 19)
  - Lundt, Alice Q. (Box 19)
  - Lutz, Frederick A. (Box 19)
  - Lyczak, Louise E. (Box 19)
  - Lyle, Floyd (Box 19)
  - Lyman, Elizabeth L. (Box 19)
  - Lyster, T. C. (Box 19)
  - M (Box 19)
  - McAreny, Wendy (Box 19)
  - McBrayer, Reuben A. (Box 19)
  - McCaffrey, Agnete L. W. (Box 19)
  - McCaffrey, Helen W. (Box 19)
  - McCarley, Susan (Box 19)
  - McCarthy, Anna (Box 19)
  - McCarthy, Anne K. (Box 19)
  - McClintock, Barbara (Box 19)
  - McConnell, Jeanette M. (Box 19)
  - McCormack, Howard (Box 19)
  - McCorkmack, Walter R. (Box 19)
  - MacCoy, Patricia (Box 19)
  - McCutcheon, Randolph (Box 19)
  - MacDonald, George (Box 19)
  - MacDonald, William J. (Box 19)
  - MacDougall, Wilhemina (Box 19)
  - McElfish, Margaret C. (Box 19)
  - McEntree, Catherine (Box 19)
  - McGill, Georgiana R. (Box 19)
  - MacGillirray, John H. (Box 19)
  - McGinnis, Kathryn (Box 19)
  - MacGrath, Joan (Box 19)
  - McGraw, Margaret (Box 19)
  - McGuire, William J. (Box 19)
  - McHugh, John F. (Box 19)
  - McIntosh, William A. (Box 19)
  - McKay, Alexander L. (Box 19)
  - MacKean, Sydney B. (Box 19)
  - Mackelburg, Walter (Box 19)
  - MacKenzie, Elizabeth (Box 19)
  - MacKenzie, John W. (Box 19)
  - Mackesy, Thomas W. (Box 19)
  - MacKinnion, Lillian (Box 19)
  - MacKenley, Earl B. (Box 19)
  - MacLaughlin, Richard (Box 19)
  - McLean, Allan (Box 19)
  - MacLeod, Elizabeth (Box 19)
  - McLeod, Elsie (Box 19)
  - McMullen, Donald B. (Box 19)
  - MacMullin, Gwendolyn (Box 19)
  - MacPherson, Daniel A. (Box 19)
  - McQuarrie, Irving (Box 19)
  - Madison, Ward N. (Box 19)
  - Maeder, LeRoy M. (Box 19)
  - Magill, Thomas P. (Box 19)
  - Magnolia, Rosemary H. (Box 19)
  - Maquire, Margie (Box 19)
  - Mahaffy, Alexander F. (Box 19)
  - Majewski, Helen (Box 19)
  - Makinsky, Alexander I. (Box 19)
  - Malave, Hector R. (Box 20)
  - Malm, Joyce C. (Box 20)
  - Manderscheid, Lester V. (Box 20)
  - Manek, Myrtle M. (Box 20)
  - Mangelsdorf, Albert J. (Box 20)
  - Mangelsdorf, Paul C. (Box 20)
  - Mangual, Rosa S. (Box 20)
  - Mann, Albert R. (Box 20)
  - Manheim, Jack Hans (Box 20)
  - Manson, Jennie E. (Box 20)
  - Manthei, Chester M. (Box 20)
  - Mao, H. C. (Box 20)
  - Marasa, Frank J. (Box 20)
  - Marchard, Doris (Box 20)
  - Marks, G. Ellis (Box 20)
  - Maroncelli, Harry J. (Box 20)
  - Marques, Edwardo (Box 20)
  - Marrero, Jose (Box 20)
  - Mars, L. D. (Box 20)
  - Marschner, Elise F. (Box 20)
  - March, Lucy (Box 20)
  - Marsh, Robert C. (Box 20)
  - Marshall, Harold K. (Box 20)
  - Marshall, Jane (Box 20)
  - Marshall, Marilyn (Box 20)
  - Martin, James (Box 20)
  - Martin, Joseph (Box 20)
  - Martin, Josephine (Box 20)
  - Martin, Kenneth (Box 20)
  - Martin, Walter B. (Box 20)
  - Martine, George W. (Box 20)
  - Martine, LeRoy (Box 20)
  - Mason, Cleon C. (Box 20)
  - Mason, Dorothy (Box 20)
  - Mason, Edward S. (Box 20)
  - Mason, Max (Box 20)
  - Massey, Barbara W. (Box 20)
  - Massey, Herbert F. (Box 20)
  - Matthews, Claudius S. (Box 20)
  - Maus, Roberta (Box 20)
  - Maxfield, Mary (Box 20)
  - May, Stacy (Box 20)
  - Mayneis, Norman (Box 20)
  - Mednis, Aiga (Box 20)
  - Meerapfel, Claire M. (Box 20)
  - Mellinger, Janice H. (Box 20)
  - Melnick, Joseph L. (Box 20)
  - Mendelson, Ralph (Box 20)
  - Merriam, Charles E. (Box 20)
  - Merten, Hedy A. (Box 20)
  - Mertz, Edwin T. (Box 20)
  - Metcalf, Keyes D. (Box 20)
  - Michailoff, Ciril D. (Box 20)
  - Michell, William (Box 20)
  - Middeleer, Marie Anne (Box 20)
  - Mieldazis, John J. (Box 20)
  - Milam, Daniel F. (Box 20)
  - Milezewski, Marion (Box 20)
  - Mildred, Laurance (Box 20)
  - Miller, Carol (Box 20)
  - Miller, Eilif (Box 20)
  - Miller, Frederick A. (Box 20)
  - Miller, Jacqueline (Box 20)
  - Miller, James A. (Box 20)
  - Miller, Jean (Box 20)
  - Miller, Margery (Box 20)
  - Millett, Fred B. (Box 21)
  - Minter, William (Box 21)
  - Mirick, Claire (Box 21)
  - Mitchell, Doris (Box 21)
  - Mitchell, Elizabeth (Box 21)
  - Mitchell, William L. (Box 21)
  - Mitchell, William L. (Mrs.) (Box 21)
  - Moe, Henry A. (Box 21)
  - Moen, Faye W. (Box 21)
  - Moger, Dorris (Box 21)
  - Malloy, Daniel M. (Box 21)
  - Malloy, Daniel M. (Mrs.) (Box 21)
  - Monahan, Kathlene F. (Box 21)
  - Monk (Mrs.) (Box 21)
  - Monroe, Willys M. (Box 21)
  - Monteas, John M. (Box 21)
  - Moore, Alice E. (Box 21)
  - Moore, Elizabeth W. (Box 21)
  - Moore, Stanford (Box 21)
  - Moose, John (Box 21)
  - Morgan, Katherine (Box 21)
  - Moriarty, Clarence F. (Box 21)
  - Moriarty, John F. (Box 21)
  - Morin, Alice (Box 21)
  - Morrell, Clarence A. (Box 21)
  - Morrison, Helen (Box 21)
  - Mosely, Phillip E. (Box 21)
  - Moser, Lawrence P. (Box 21)
  - Mueller, Mary E. (Box 21)
  - Muench, Hugo (Box 21)
  - Mulhern, Joan (Box 22)
  - Mullen, Charles J. (Box 22)
  - Muller, Henry R. (Box 22)
  - Mumford, Melba (Box 22)
  - Munn, Robert F. (Box 22)
  - Murphy, James D. (Box 22)
  - Murphy, Marlene L. (Box 22)
  - Murphy, Peggy R. (Box 22)
  - Murphy, Vincent (Box 22)
  - Myers, Elizabeth I. (Box 22)
  - Myers, Louis G. (Box 22)
  - Myers, Virginia (Box 22)
  - Myers, W. I. (Box 22)
  - N (Box 22)
  - Nabrit, Samuel N. (Box 22)
  - Nash, Isabel (Box 22)
  - Navy, Muriel (Box 22)
  - Neill, Nancy (Box 22)
  - Nesius, Ernest (Box 22)
  - Neuhauser, Joan (Box 22)
  - Newcomb, Warner H. (Box 22)
  - Nicholas, Shelush (Box 22)
  - Nicholls, Gertrude (Box 22)
  - Nightingale, Harold (Box 22)
  - Nipps, Helen S. (Box 22)
  - Nixon, Betty (Box 22)
  - Noble, Robert E. (Box 22)
  - Nolan, Thomas B. (Box 22)
  - Norris, Wiliam P. (Box 22)
  - Noll, Alice C. (Box 22)
  - Noll, Anna M. (Box 22)
  - Norton, Thomas F. (Box 22)
  - Notkin, Ann Terry (Box 22)
  - O (Box 22)
  - Oberman, Carmen L. (Box 22)
  - O'Brien, Daniel P. (Box 22)
  - O'Brien, Henry R. (Box 22)
  - Obringer, Virginia (Box 22)
  - O'Connell, Geraldine (Box 22)
  - O'Connor, Francis W. (Box 22)
  - O'Connor, Kathleen (Box 22)
  - Ogden, Elizabeth H. (Box 22)
  - Ohlander, Carolyn (Box 22)
  - Ohlson, Virginia M. (Box 22)
  - Ohlsson, Elizabeth (Box 22)
  - Okajima, Hideo (Box 22)
  - O'Keefe,Elizabeth (Box 22)
  - Old, H. Norman (Box 22)
  - Olinger, Meredith (Box 22)
  - Oliver, Francis (Box 22)
  - Omura, Yoko (Box 22)
  - Ondics, Eleanor (Box 22)
  - Opie, Eugene L. (Box 22)
  - Orr, Dorothy (Box 22)
  - Ortiz, Gabriel (Box 22)
  - Osborn, Eleanor (Box 22)
  - Otterson, Lillian (Box 22)
  - P (Box 22)
  - Pace, Harry A. Stuart, Jr. (Box 22)
  - Padron, Mauro (Box 22)
  - Paige, Eugene (Box 22)
  - Palazzo, Frank (Box 22)
  - Parker, Cora (Box 22)
  - Parker, George (Box 22)
  - Parran, Thomas (Box 22)
  - Parsons, Ethel (Box 22)
  - Paterson, Betty (Box 22)
  - Patino, Jose Felix (Box 22)
  - Patten, Bradley M. (Box 22)
  - Patterson, Fredrick Douglas (Box 22)
  - Patterson, Mary J. (Box 22)
  - Paul, George P. (Box 23)
  - Paul, John H. (Box 23)
  - Payne, George C. (Box 23)
  - Paulsen, Frannces (Box 23)
  - Pearce, Richard M. and Mrs. R. M. (Box 23)
  - Pearse, A. S. (Box 23)
  - Pederson, Ruth (Box 23)
  - Pegeron, Vincent (Box 23)
  - Pendery, Marcelle (Box 23)
  - Pepper, Mary L. (Box 23)
  - Percudani, Mathilda (Box 23)
  - Pereira, Carlos A. (Box 23)
  - Pernambuco. Mario (Box 23)
  - Peterson, Eleanor (Box 23)
  - Peterson, M. L. (Box 23)
  - Peterson, Mary (Box 23)
  - Petritz, Louis J. (Box 23)
  - Pfeiffer, A. C. (Box 23)
  - Phair, John (Box 23)
  - Philip, Cornelius B. (Box 23)
  - Phillips, Nancy (Box 23)
  - Phillips, Roseanna (Box 23)
  - Pickels, Edward G. (Box 23)
  - Pickering, Frances (Box 23)
  - Pierce, Harry M. (Box 23)
  - Pierce, Ruth (Box 23)
  - Pierpoint, Ruth (Box 23)
  - Pincock, Karma (Box 23)
  - Pitcher, Herbert (Box 23)
  - Pitner, John B. (Box 23)
  - Place, Herman G. (Box 24)
  - Platt, Donald (Box 24)
  - Platte, Dorothy (Box 24)
  - Poleman, Thomas T. (Box 24)
  - Polk, James R. (Box 24)
  - Pomeranz, Yeshajahu (Box 24)
  - Pompenoe, Hugh (Box 24)
  - Popper, Eleanor D. (Box 24)
  - Porter, Adriennce (Box 24)
  - Porter, Claire R. (Box 24)
  - Pothier, Oliver L. (Box 24)
  - Pott, Walter H. (Box 24)
  - Potter, Catherine (Box 24)
  - Poulos, Gloria (Box 24)
  - Powell, Carl A. (Box 24)
  - Presson, Virgil G. (Box 24)
  - Price, Helen (Box 24)
  - Price, Patricia R. (Box 24)
  - Prinzivalli, Robert (Box 24)
  - Proctor, George (Box 24)
  - Pullen, Bertha (Box 24)
  - Putnam, Persis (Box 24)
  - Pye, Mildred S. (Box 24)
  - Pyros, Silvia (Box 24)
  - Q (Box 24)
  - Quarles, Anne (Box 24)
  - R (Box 24)
  - Rabier, Helen A. (Box 24)
  - Racusin, Suzanne (Box 24)
  - Ramirez, Mary (Box 24)
  - Ramirez, Rafela (Box 24)
  - Ramsamooj, Elaine (Box 24)
  - Ramsdell, Christine (Box 24)
  - Ramsey, George H. (Box 24)
  - Ranklin, Howard P. (Box 24)
  - Ratchford, C. Brice (Box 24)
  - Raun, Esther (Box 24)
  - Rauschenbach, Mary (Box 24)
  - Reagan, Reginald (Box 24)
  - Reardon, Betty Ann (Box 24)
  - Rector, Nelson A. (Box 24)
  - Redman, Mary J. (Box 24)
  - Reed, Ruth (Box 24)
  - Reges, Jean M. (Box 24)
  - Reid, Wendell (Box 24)
  - Reilly, Madeline C. (Box 24)
  - Reinhard, Otto OA. (Box 24)
  - Reitch, Dorothy (Box 24)
  - Reker, Martha C. (Box 24)
  - Reynolds, Rachel (Box 24)
  - Ricci, Nelda E. (Box 24)
  - Rice, John L. (Box 24)
  - Rice, Justus B. (Box 24)
  - Rich, Alan (Box 24)
  - Richardson, Luella (Box 24)
  - Richardson, Martha (Box 24)
  - Rikard, Elsemere R. (Box 24)
  - Riehl, Louis A. (Box 24)
  - Riehl, Louis H. (Box 24)
  - Rigney, Betty Lou (Box 24)
  - Ritchie, Elizabeth M. (Box 25)
  - Robbins, Noel (Box 25)
  - Robbins, William J. (Box 25)
  - Roberts, Frank L. (Box 25)
  - Robels, Angel (Box 25)
  - Robinson, Edith (Box 25)
  - Robinson, Harold F. (Box 25)
  - Robinson, Peggy (Box 25)
  - Robinson, William D. (Box 25)
  - Rocafort, Frank J. (Box 25)
  - Roche, Besse (Box 25)
  - Rockwell, Mary E. (Box 25)
  - Rockwell, France (Box 25)
  - Rodman, Barbara T. (Box 25)
  - Rodriquez, Camello (Box 25)
  - Rodriquez, Eucides (Box 25)
  - Rodriquez, Nydis (Box 25)
  - Rodriquez, Ovidio (Box 25)
  - Rodriquez, William (Box 25)
  - Roest, Dorothy (Box 25)
  - Rogers, Ruth (Box 25)
  - Roman, Doris (Box 25)
  - Roman, Juan (Box 25)
  - Roome, Barbara (Box 25)
  - Rooney, J. Laurence (Box 25)
  - Rooney, Walter (Box 25)
  - Roorda, Anna R. (Box 25)
  - Root, Francis M. (Box 25)
  - Ropes, William (Box 25)
  - Rosado, Ada (Box 25)
  - Rosado, Pedro (Box 25)
  - Rose, Charlotte (Box 25)
  - Rose, Wickliffe (Box 25)
  - Rosen, Sonya (Box 25)
  - Rosenbush, Robert A. (Box 25)
  - Ross, Alberta (Box 25)
  - Ross, Jean (Box 25)
  - Ross, Judith (Box 25)
  - Rossi, Arnalda G. (Box 25)
  - Rossman, Sally I. (Box 25)
  - Rous, Palmer (Box 25)
  - Rowan, W. H. (Box 25)
  - Rowland, Lauretta (Box 25)
  - Royhl, Mary M. (Box 25)
  - Rubianes, Augustina (Box 25)
  - Rullo, Guy (Box 25)
  - Rumsey, Virgina I. (Box 25)
  - Rush, James E. (Box 25)
  - Russell, Frederick F. (Box 25)
  - Russell, Gladys (Box 25)
  - Russell, Morell B. (Box 25)
  - Russell, Norman H. (Box 25)
  - Rutter, Elizabeth (Box 25)
  - Ryan, Bryce (Box 25)
  - Ryan, Mary L. (Box 25)
  - S (Box 25)
  - Sadun, Elvio L. (Box 25)
  - Safford, Evelyn (Box 25)
  - Saito, Charles (Box 25)
  - Salant, Walter (Box 25)
  - Salas, Judith (Box 25)
  - Sams, Joseph (Box 25)
  - Sanders, Morris B. (Box 25)
  - Sandrik, Maria T. (Box 25)
  - Santiago, Ruben (Box 26)
  - Sapir, Philip (Box 26)
  - Sargent, Clealand A. (Box 26)
  - Sasse, Bruce E. (Box 26)
  - Saunders, Andrew (Box 26)
  - Saunders, George M. (Box 26)
  - Saville, Thordike (Box 26)
  - Sawyer, Wilbur A. (Box 26)
  - Sayre, Gertrude (Box 26)
  - Sbarge, Anne K. (Box 26)
  - Scala, Michael E. (Box 26)
  - Scannell, Edward (Box 26)
  - Schaer, William G. (Box 26)
  - Schapiro, Louis (Box 26)
  - Scheffer, Irene (Box 26)
  - Schmidt, Conrad (Box 26)
  - Schneider, Alan (Box 26)
  - Schoonmaker, Betsy (Box 26)
  - Schorske, Carl E. (Box 26)
  - Schrade, Margaret L. (Box 26)
  - Schultz, Edwin W. (Box 26)
  - Schultz, Theodore W. (Box 26)
  - Schwab, Mary B. (Box 26)
  - Schwinler, Helen (Box 26)
  - Schwentker, Francis F. (Box 26)
  - Sciacca, Mary (Box 26)
  - Scott, James A. (Box 26)
  - Scott, Lois H. (Box 26)
  - Scott, Margaret A. (Box 26)
  - Scott, Walter O. (Box 26)
  - Scott, W. J. (Box 26)
  - Scupham, George W. (Box 26)
  - Sealey, Henry J. (Box 26)
  - Seilberger, Eugene (Box 26)
  - Sells, Sally (Box 26)
  - Semel, Shirley (Box 26)
  - Sentz, James C. (Box 26)
  - Sesisto, Edith (Box 27)
  - Shannon, Raymond C. (Box 27)
  - Sharp, Robert L. (Box 27)
  - Shaw, Frank R. (Box 27)
  - Sheldon, Mary (Box 27)
  - Shell, Elizabeth (Box 27)
  - Sheppard, Charlotte (Box 27)
  - Shilling, Anne (Box 27)
  - Shoolangin, Valentine (Box 27)
  - Shore, Clarence A. (Box 27)
  - Shumate, Eva (Box 27)
  - Siddron, Joseph (Box 27)
  - Sidney, Evelyn (Box 27)
  - Silver, Selma R. (Box 27)
  - Simpson, Dorothy (Box 27)
  - Simpson, Earline D. (Box 27)
  - Sisco, Dwight L. (Box 27)
  - Slavvin, Dorothy (Box 27)
  - Smillie, Jean (Box 27)
  - Smillie, Wilson G. (Box 27)
  - Smith, Arthur C. (Box 27)
  - Smith, Doris R. (Box 27)
  - Smith, Fay (Box 27)
  - Smith, Hugh H. (Box 27)
  - Smith, Jeanne (Box 27)
  - Smith, Luciane (Box 27)
  - Smith, Patricia (Box 27)
  - Smith, Windsor (Box 27)
  - Smithburn, Kenneth (Box 27)
  - Smither, Catherine (Box 27)
  - Snodgrass, John E. (Box 27)
  - Snyder, Jean C. (Box 27)
  - Snyder, John C. (Box 27)
  - Socol, Jacqueline (Box 27)
  - Sokoloff, Joan (Box 27)
  - Soley, Barbara (Box 27)
  - Soper, Fred L. (Box 27)
  - Soules, James T. (Box 28)
  - Southard, W. W. (Box 28)
  - Souza, G. Paula (Box 28)
  - Sowell, Thomas (Box 28)
  - Spalvins, Inara (Box 28)
  - Sparks, Alton Neal (Box 28)
  - Spatola, James F. (Box 28)
  - Spengler, Joseph J. (Box 28)
  - Spooner, Phyllis N. (Box 28)
  - Sporn, Deborah (Box 28)
  - Sprague, George F. (Box 28)
  - Staack, Murtle (Box 28)
  - Stainsby, Wendell J. (Box 28)
  - Stearns, Barbara (Box 28)
  - Stevens, David H. (Box 28)
  - Steck, Eisbeth (Box 28)
  - Steel, Ernst W. (Box 28)
  - Steinberg, Michael (Box 28)
  - Steininger, Anna (Box 28)
  - Stegmaier, Ann (Box 28)
  - Stephan, Frederick F. (Box 28)
  - Stevens, Marion (Box 28)
  - Steves, Marylousie (Box 28)
  - Stewart, Jane (Box 28)
  - Stewart, John B. (Box 28)
  - Stewart, Malcolm (Box 28)
  - Stewart, Marcelle (Box 28)
  - Stewart, Martha M. (Box 28)
  - Stewart, Walter W. (Box 28)
  - Stocker, Sonya (Box 28)
  - Stokes, Adrian (Box 28)
  - Stone, Alyce (Box 28)
  - Stone, Bernard (Box 28)
  - Stoops, Irene Christiansen (Box 28)
  - Stout, Charlotte (Box 28)
  - Stover, Laura (Box 28)
  - Stratman, Thomas W. (Box 28)
  - Strode, George K. (Box 28)
  - Strom, Robert (Box 28)
  - Stroud, Robert C. (Box 28)
  - Struse, Alvin M. (Box 28)
  - Struthers, Robert R. (Box 28)
  - Stryker, Norma (Box 28)
  - Stuart, Corinne M. (Box 28)
  - Sullivan, Anne Marie (Box 28)
  - Sutherland, Kenneth H. (Box 28)
  - Swartley, Joyce (Box 28)
  - Sweet, Winfield C. (Box 28)
  - Swigert, Jean (Box 29)
  - Sykes, Katherine (Box 29)
  - Sykora, Wynifred (Box 29)
  - T (Box 29)
  - Taber, Elizabeth (Box 29)
  - Tallerday, Eileen A. (Box 29)
  - Tallon, Edward J. (Box 29)
  - Talmadge, Marvin B. (Box 29)
  - Tangney, Constance M. (Box 29)
  - Talcott, Joan (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Carl E. (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Dorothy (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Douglas (Miss) (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Hurbie A. (Box 29)
  - Taylor, James B. (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Lee B. (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Richard M. (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Ruth G. (Box 29)
  - Templeton, James D. (Box 29)
  - Tennant, B. C. (Box 29)
  - Tennant, Mary E. (Box 29)
  - Thaw, Beatrice (Box 29)
  - Thompson, Alice Mary (Box 29)
  - Thompson, Elizabeth (Box 29)
  - Thompson, Helen (Box 29)
  - Thompson, Jean (Box 29)
  - Thompson, Jeanne (Box 29)
  - Thompson, Joan H. (Box 29)
  - Thompson, Norma (Box 29)
  - Thompson, Patricia (Box 29)
  - Thompson, Ruth (Box 29)
  - Thornton, Constance D. (Box 29)
  - Thornton, Sylvia (Box 29)
  - Tudman, Walter D. (Box 29)
  - Tisdale, Alfred D. (Box 29)
  - Tisdale, Wilbur E. (Box 29)
  - Tolliver, Benjamin (Box 29)
  - Tooker, Eileen K. (Box 29)
  - Toorey, Hetty (Box 29)
  - Trachtenberg, Vita (Box 29)
  - Tracy, Barbara J. (Box 29)
  - Traynor, Alice (Box 29)
  - Traynor, Margaret Mary (Box 29)
  - Tribe, Derek E. (Box 29)
  - Trinka, Bedrick (Box 29)
  - Trotter, Mildred (Box 29)
  - Tryon, Katherine (Box 30)
  - Tschundi, Verena (Box 30)
  - Tucker, Clarence (Box 30)
  - Tully, Doris (Box 30)
  - Tupper, Margaret (Box 30)
  - Turner, Thomas B. (Box 30)
  - Turnquest, Howard (Box 30)
  - Twombly, Ann W. (Box 30)
  - Tyler, Mary W. (Box 30)
  - Utzinger, Otto E. (Box 30)
  - V (Box 30)
  - Valentine, Ramon (Box 30)
  - VanDeest, Jeane (Box 30)
  - Vandellos, Nuria (Box 30)
  - Van Dyke, Willard (Box 30)
  - Van Gelder, Agnew (Box 30)
  - Van Hoogendyk, Marianna (Box 30)
  - Van Ness, Jean (Box 30)
  - Van Noort, Cornelius (Box 30)
  - Van Sickle, John R. (Box 30)
  - Van Valkenburg, Vivian A. (Box 30)
  - Van Wesep, Henry B. (Box 30)
  - Varley, Margaret L. (Box 30)
  - Vaughn, Emmett I. (Box 30)
  - Vehe, Karl L. (Box 30)
  - Velez, Iris V. (Box 30)
  - Viatkin, Olga J. (Box 30)
  - Vincent, George E. (Box 30)
  - Vieira, Francisco B. (Box 30)
  - Visher, John W. (Box 30)
  - Vissokovsky, Nikolai (Box 30)
  - Vogt, Ruth (Box 30)
  - Von Engelhardt, Konstantin (Box 30)
  - Von Sholly, Virginia (Box 30)
  - Vontill, Elizabeth (Box 30)
  - Vorbach, Evelyn G. (Box 30)
  - Voris, Ellnor J. (Box 30)
  - W (Box 30)
  - Wagner, Ruth (Box 30)
  - Waide, Helen (Box 30)
  - Waite, J. Herbert (Box 30)
  - Wakeman, A. Maurice (Box 30)
  - Wakeman, A. Maurice (Mrs.) (Box 30)
  - Walcott, Allen M. (Box 30)
  - Wales, Georgia (Box 30)
  - Walker, June W. (Box 30)
  - Walker, Sydnor H. (Box 30)
  - Wall, Marion (Box 31)
  - Wallace, Frank W. (Box 31)
  - Wallace, James (Box 31)
  - Walling, Mary Roberts (Box 31)
  - Walsh, Helen (Box 31)
  - Walther, Jean (Box 31)
  - Ward, Grace (Box 31)
  - Warren, Andrew J. (Box 31)
  - Warren, Shields (Box 31)
  - Washburn, Benjamin E. (Box 31)
  - Washington, James (Box 31)
  - Waters, Paul (Box 31)
  - Waters. Warren (Box 31)
  - Watkins, Richard W. (Box 31)
  - Weathersbee, Albert A. (Box 31)
  - Weber, Harold (Box 31)
  - Webster, Katherine (Box 31)
  - Wector, Dixon (Box 31)
  - Weed, Priscilla (Box 31)
  - Weir, Andrew F. (Box 31)
  - Welker, Mary Joan (Box 31)
  - Wells, Clifford W. (Box 31)
  - Wensley, Martha (Box 31)
  - West, Doris (Box 31)
  - Whalen, John (Box 31)
  - Wheatley, Barbara (Box 31)
  - Wheeler, Charles M. (Box 31)
  - Whelan, Ruth (Box 31)
  - Whidden, Marion (Box 31)
  - White, Gilbert F. (Box 31)
  - White, Eleanor (Box 31)
  - White, Elise (Box 31)
  - White, Joseph H. (Box 31)
  - White, Phyllis (Box 31)
  - Whitelaw, Robert N. S. (Box 31)
  - Whitford, Sarah (Box 31)
  - Whitmore, Eugene R. (Box 31)
  - Whitney, Elizabeth L. (Box 31)
  - Wilfred, Thomas C. (Box 31)
  - Wille, Vivian B. (Box 31)
  - Williams, Linsly R. (Box 31)
  - Williams, Shirley Anne (Box 32)
  - Williamson, Francis (Box 32)
  - Willits, Joseph H. (Box 32)
  - Wilson, David B. (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Eleanor (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Janet B. (Box 32)
  - Wilson, Richard (Box 32)
  - Wing, Wilson M. (Box 32)
  - Wingate, Abram R., Jr. (Box 32)
  - Winkin, Jean M. (Box 32)
  - Winsor, Sanford A. (Box 32)
  - Wirth, Dorothy (Box 32)
  - Wiszuk, Peter P. (Box 32)
  - Wittwer, Sylvan H. (Box 32)
  - Wolfenson, Frances (Box 32)
  - Wong, Fue Lang (Box 32)
  - Wood, James B. (Box 32)
  - Wright, Daniel E. (Box 32)
  - Wright, Emily (Box 32)
  - Wright, Grace (Box 32)
  - Wright, Nadene (Box 32)
  - Wrightson, William D. (Box 32)
  - Wyatt, Bernard L. (Box 32)
  - Y (Box 32)
  - Yates, Peter (Box 32)
  - Yaeger, Clark H. (Box 32)
  - Yen, F. C. (Box 32)
  - Yochelson, Sally (Box 32)
  - Young, Geoffrey W. (Box 32)
  - Young, Harry C. (Box 32)
  - Young, Hong Yip (Box 32)
  - Youngs, Harry Hill, Jr. (Box 32)
  - Z (Box 32)
  - Zerbey. Esther (Box 32)
  - Zethraus, Ivy (Box 32)
  - Zither, Dona (Box 32)
  - Zoglin, Mary (Box 32)
  - Zorn, Gertrude (Box 32)
  - Zulch, Walter (Box 32)
  - Zwirlein, Thomas C. (Box 32)
- Staff, A-Z, 1951-1960; 2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
  - Aharonian, Natalie (Box 33)
  - Appel, Barbara (Box 33)
  - Applewaite, Eleanor (Box 33)
  - Ardissone, Edith Ann (Box 33)
  - Arrathoon, Maro (Mrs. Goldstone) (Box 33)
  - Bagley, Darnell (Box 33)
  - Barber, Reva (Box 33)
  - Barry, Audrey J. (Box 33)
  - Barry, Harriet C. (Mrs. Robert Barry) (Box 33)
  - Bateman, Katherine (Mrs. Jim Cassidy) (Box 33)
  - Bauer, Florence B. (Box 33)
  - Benedict, Mary A. (Box 33)
  - Bergeron, Anne (Box 33)
  - Bielitz, Martha (Box 33)
  - Birchall, Jeanne (Box 33)
  - Boe, Edmund S. (Box 33)
  - Bordage, Judith W. (Box 33)
  - Brandt, Helene (Box 33)
  - Brandwein, Lisa R. (Box 33)
  - Brewster, Isabel E. (Box 33)
  - Briody, James F. (Box 33)
  - Brooke, Mary G. (Box 33)
  - Brown, Harriette J. (Box 33)
  - Buck, Martha (Box 33)
  - Burkhalter, Betty B. (Box 33)
  - Byrnes, William (Box 33)
  - Campbell, Dorothy (Box 33)
  - Campbell, Janet I. (Box 33)
  - Chidsey. Ann B. (Box 33)
  - Cloutier, Dorothy (Box 33)
  - Combopiano, Charles A. (Box 33)
  - Conner, Barbara Ann (Box 33)
  - Corboy, Mona (Box 33)
  - Corey, Ellen M. (Box 33)
  - Cornwell, Vera A. (Box 33)
  - Cosman, Tania M. (Box 33)
  - Curry, Eugenia (Box 33)
  - Cygenhagen, Veronica Henderson (Box 33)
  - Dawson, Anne B. (Box 33)
  - De Foe, Phoebe (Box 33)
  - De Virgilio, Minnie (Box 33)
  - Diggs, Elizabeth S. (Box 33)
  - Dormody, Pamela (Box 33)
  - Drake, Kent L. (Box 33)
  - Dreyer, Rosemary A. (Box 33)
  - Ducey, Martha M. (Box 33)
  - Eareckson, Virginia (Box 33)
  - Earich, Janet M. (Box 33)
  - Earle, Audrey (Box 33)
  - Eiseman, Ellen (Box 33)
  - Eldridge, Thomas (Box 33)
  - Ericson, Roy A. (Box 33)
  - Ervin, Faith T. (Box 33)
  - Evelyn, Elton (Box 33)
  - Ewing, Jane K. (Box 33)
  - Fastaia, Anthony J. (Box 33)
  - Fedewicz, Theodore (Box 33)
  - Fernandez, Anthony O. (Box 33)
  - Ffennell, Jennifer J. (Box 33)
  - Fisher, Barbara (Box 33)
  - Fitzgerald, Israel L. (Box 33)
  - Fitzhugh, James (Box 33)